Guide to the Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
Bambaataa, Afrika hip hop archive,
- Series IX. Music Collection
  - 12 inch Vinyl
    - Not annotated
      - P
        - Peebles, Ann - If this is heaven, 1977; SR-25088; Peebles, Ann (Box 386)
          Catalog # HLP-6002; A-side Matrix # H-6002-A
          Hi Records
        - Peewee In The Newz - Keep dancin', 1983; SR-23261; Peewee In The Newz; Pee Wee; Ford, Pee Wee (Box 386)
          Catalog # NR1002; A-side Matrix # NR 1002 A
          N.A.M.E. Brand Records
        - Peewee In The Newz - Keep dancin', 1983; SR-23262; Peewee In The Newz; Pee Wee; Ford, Pee Wee (Box 386)
        - Penalty Phase - Lightning seeds of life, 1995; SR-23263; Penalty Phase (Box 386)
          Catalog # DOS 013-1; A-side Matrix # PENALTY PHASE A1
          Dos Or Die Recordings
        - Penda, Hilaire - Jungle people, 1985; SR-23264; Penda, Hilaire (Box 386)
          Catalog # 27254; A-side Matrix # 27254 A AM
          Panthere Production
          Rouen, France
        - Pendergrass, Teddy - Only you; Get up, get down, get funky, get loose, 1978; SR-23265; Pendergrass, Teddy (Box 386)
          Catalog # 2Z8 3655; A-side Matrix # P.I.R. XSS-164792-1A
        - Pendergrass, Teddy - Joy, 1988; SR-23266; Pendergrass, Teddy (Box 387)
          Catalog # 0-66766; A-side Matrix # STED-66766-A1 1-1
        - Pendergrass, Teddy - Love 4/2, 1985; SR-23267; Pendergrass, Teddy (Box 387)
          Catalog # ED 5119; A-side Matrix # ST-ED-5119-A-1 1-1
          Asylum Records
        - Pendergrass, Teddy - You're my choice tonight (choose me), 1984; SR-23268; Pendergrass, Teddy (Box 387)
          Catalog # ED 5008; A-side Matrix # ST-ED-5008-A1 1-1
        - Pendergrass, Teddy - Joy, 1988; SR-23269; Pendergrass, Teddy (Box 387)
          Catalog # ED 5298; A-side Matrix # STED-5298-A1 1-1
        - Pendergrass, Teddy - Believe in love, 1993; SR-23270; Pendergrass, Teddy (Box 387)
          Catalog # 0-66227; A-side Matrix # ST-ED-5681 DMM A1 SP1-1 RB
        - Pendergrass, Teddy - Greatest hits, 1984; SR-23271; Pendergrass, Teddy (Box 387)
          Catalog # FZ 39252; A-side Matrix # AL 39252-1A
          New York City, New York
        - Pendergrass, Teddy - Joy, 1988; SR-23272; Pendergrass, Teddy (Box 387)
          Catalog # 60775-1; A-side Matrix # STE 60775 A-2 DMM SP1-6
        - Pendergrass, Teddy - Joy, 1988; SR-23273; Pendergrass, Teddy (Box 387)
        - Pendergrass, Teddy - The very best of Teddy, 2000; SR-23274; Pendergrass, Teddy (Box 387)
          In same jacket as # SR-23275. 2 copies.Test Pressing
          Catalog # DISCO-14; A-side Matrix # DISCO-14-A
        - Pendergrass, Teddy - The very best of Teddy, 2000; SR-23275; Pendergrass, Teddy (Box 387)
          In same jacket as # SR-23274. 2 copies.Test Pressing
        - Pendergrass, Teddy - Love T.K.O., 1980; SR-23276; Pendergrass, Teddy (Box 387)
          Catalog # AS 861; A-side Matrix # P.I.R. AA-XSS-167789
        - Pendergrass, Teddy - Take me in your arms tonight, 1980; SR-23277; Pendergrass, Teddy; Mills, Stephanie (Box 387)
          Catalog # 4Z8 01059; A-side Matrix # P.I.R. AB-4Z8-01059-4
        - Penguin - What sweet in goat mouth, 1983; SR-23278; Penguin; Paul, Leston (Box 387)
          Catalog # BSR 1030; A-side Matrix # BSR 1030 A
        - Peniston, CeCe - Keep givin' me your love remixes, 1994; SR-23279; Peniston, CeCe (Box 387)
          Catalog # CAS 6727; A-side Matrix # XSS-6727-A 1B
        - Penn, Dawn - You don't love me (no, no, no), 1993; SR-23280; Penn, Dawn (Box 387)
          Catalog # 0-10151; A-side Matrix # ST-DM-70595-70596-70593-1 1-1
          Big Beat
        - Penn, Kristin - Evergreen; Electric boogie, 1985; SR-23281; Penn, Kristin (Box 387)
          Catalog #; A-side Matrix # GBI-224-90-A
          G.B.I. Recording Co. Ltd.
          Freeport, Bahamas
        - Pensador, Gabriel O - Ainda é só o começo (disc one), 1995; SR-23282; Pensador, Gabriel O (Box 387)
          In same jacket as # SR-23283. Double album.
          Catalog # 231.284; A-side Matrix # JB 231284/1-479069 A XSB-4268 (P) 1995
          Chaos
        - Pensador, Gabriel O - Ainda é só o começo (disc two), 1995; SR-23283; Pensador, Gabriel O (Box 387)
          In same jacket as # SR-23282. Double album.
          Catalog # 231.285; A-side Matrix # JB 231285/1-479069 A XSB-4277 (P) 1995
        - Penthouse 4 - Bust this house down (remix), 1988; SR-23284; Penthouse 4 (Box 387)
          Catalog # 12SYX 10; A-side Matrix # 12SYX 10 A-1-1-
          Syncopate
        - Penthouse Players Clique - P.S. play u 2; P.L.F., 1992; SR-23285; Penthouse Players Clique (Box 387)
          Catalog # SPRO 6633; A-side Matrix # S-26779 SPRO-6633-AZ1
        - People Under The Stairs - Acid raindrops, 2002; SR-23286; People Under The Stairs (Box 387)
          Catalog # OM-124SV; A-side Matrix # OM 124SV-A
          OM Records
        - People Under The Stairs - Jappy jap, 2002; SR-23287; People Under The Stairs (Box 387)
          Catalog # OM-107SV; A-side Matrix # OM-107-SV-A LOUD
        - People Under The Stairs - O.S.T., 2002; SR-23288; People Under The Stairs (Box 387)
          Catalog # OM-109SV; A-side Matrix # OM-109-SV-A LOUD
        - People's Choice - Can't get enough of your love, 1984; SR-23289; People's Choice (Box 387)
          Catalog # PRO 280-1; A-side Matrix # PRO 280-12-57855 PRC-C 1-1-1 A
          Mercury
        - Pepe Kale - Pon moun paka bougé, 1989; SR-23290; Pepe Kale (Box 387)
          Catalog # AR 1007; A-side Matrix # 89 1 AR 1007 A AM
          Afro-Rythmes
        - Peplab - Ride the pony (part 1), 1999; SR-23291; Peplab (Box 387)
          In same jacket as # SR-23292. Different discs.
          Catalog # DAN 667156 6; A-side Matrix # 667 1566 A 2
          Dance Pool
        - Peplab - Ride the pony (part 2), 1999; SR-23292; Peplab (Box 387)
          In same jacket as # SR-23291. Different discs.
          Catalog # DAN 667156 8; A-side Matrix # 667 156 8 A
        - Pepper - Roller skating (with you); Up in flames, 1979; SR-23293; Pepper (Box 387)
          Catalog # NOYB-2201; A-side Matrix # NOYB-2201-A
          None Of Your Business Records
        - Pepsi & Shirlie - All right now, 1987; SR-23294; Pepsi & Shirlie (Box 387)
          Catalog # 887 277-1; A-side Matrix # 887277 1 A 87NP 7482
        - Pepsi & Shirlie - All right now, 1987; SR-23295; Pepsi & Shirlie (Box 387)
        - Per Cussion - Everybody's talking, 1986; SR-23296; Per Cussion (Box 387)
          Catalog # SRS 4704; A-side Matrix # SRS 4704 A
          Silence
          Koppom, Sweden
        - Per Cussion - Beatwave, 1984; SR-23297; Per Cussion (Box 387)
          Catalog # SRS 4692; A-side Matrix # SRS 4692 A BLK LP 001-A
        - Per Cussion - Don't stop, 1987; SR-23298; Per Cussion (Box 387)
          Catalog # FOG 86 007; A-side Matrix # 76.44705-01A1
          Fog Records
        - Per Cussion All Stars - Payin' the price!, 1984; SR-23299; Per Cussion All Stars (Box 387)
          Catalog # XING 127; A-side Matrix # XING 127 A
        - Perez, Julian "Jumpin" - Ain't we funky now, 1988; SR-23300; Perez, Julian "Jumpin" (Box 387)
          Catalog # DJ-977; A-side Matrix # DJ-977-A
          D.J. International Records
          Chicago, Illinois
        - Perfect Gentlemen - Don't forget to call, 1993; SR-23301; Perfect Gentlemen (Box 387)
          Catalog # PRO-A-6331; A-side Matrix # PRO-A1-6331-SR1 1-1
        - Perfect Touch - Listen to my heartbeat, 1987; SR-23302; Perfect Touch (Box 387)
          Catalog # SPR 12-429; A-side Matrix # 1897-SPR-12429-A
          Spring Records
        - Perlman, Dan - You know me, I know you, 1979; SR-23303; Perlman, Dan (Box 387)
          Catalog # FLP 254 L; A-side Matrix # SLP-254-A
          Laser Records
        - Perry, Greg - It takes heart, 1982; SR-23304; Perry, Greg (Box 387)
          Catalog # AAD-14017; A-side Matrix # M-14017-BS M 2 MR 25442X
          Alfa
        - Perry, Lee - Dreadlocks in moonlight; Ooh! Waah!, 1982; SR-23305; Perry, Lee; Fabulous Five (Box 387)
          Catalog # MLPS 7796; A-side Matrix # MLPS-7796-A
          Mango
        - Perry, Lee - Dreadlocks in moonlight; Ooh! Waah!, 1982; SR-23306; Perry, Lee; Fabulous Five (Box 387)
        - Perry, Lee - Time boom x de devil dead, 1987; SR-23307; Perry, Lee; Dub Syndicate (Box 387)
          Catalog # SYLP 6000; A-side Matrix # SYLP 6000 A-1-1-2-
        - Perry, Paula - Extra, extra, 1998; SR-23308; Perry, Paula (Box 387)
          Catalog # 374633043-1; A-side Matrix # 374633043-1A
          Mad Sounds Recordings
        - Perry, Paula - Extra, extra, 1998; SR-23309; Perry, Paula (Box 387)
        - Perry, Steve - Oh Sherrie, 1984; SR-23310; Perry, Steve (Box 387)
          Catalog # AS 1841; A-side Matrix # XSS 169623 1A
        - Persuasions - Spread the word, 1972; SR-23311; Persuasions (Box 387)
          Catalog # ST-11101; A-side Matrix # ST-1-11101-F2
        - Persuasions - Street corner symphony, 1972; SR-23312; Persuasions (Box 387)
          Catalog # ST-872; A-side Matrix # ST-1-872 H-6#1
        - Persuit - Persuit Strange EP, 2000; SR-23313; Persuit (Box 387)
          Test Pressing
          Catalog #; A-side Matrix #
        - Pet Shop Boys - It's a sin, 1987; SR-23314; Pet Shop Boys (Box 387)
          Catalog # V-19256; A-side Matrix # B-28271-Z1 V-1-19256-Z1
          EMI America
        - Pet Shop Boys - What have I done to deserve this?; Rent, 1988; SR-23315; Pet Shop Boys (Box 387)
          Catalog # SPRO-04013; A-side Matrix # 1-2 SPRO-04013-Z2 19139 0- B-29957-Z2
          EMI-Manhattan Records
        - Pet Shop Boys - Heart (remix), 1988; SR-23316; Pet Shop Boys (Box 387)
          Catalog # K 060-20 2550 6; A-side Matrix # 2025506-A1
          Parlophone
        - Pet Shop Boys - DJ culture; Music for boys, 1991; SR-23317; Pet Shop Boys (Box 388)
          Catalog # V-56234; A-side Matrix # V-1-56234-Z2
          EMI USA
        - Pet Shop Boys - Opportunities (let's make lots of money), 1986; SR-23318; Pet Shop Boys (Box 388)
          In same jacket as # SR-23319. 2 copies. Annotated.
          Catalog # V-19215; A-side Matrix # AL-SP 1-1-19215-P-2 O B-23784-P2 12776
        - Pet Shop Boys - Opportunities (let's make lots of money), 1986; SR-23319; Pet Shop Boys (Box 388)
          In same jacket as # SR-23318. 2 copies.
        - Pet Shop Boys - London, 2002; SR-23320; Pet Shop Boys (Box 388)
          Catalog # 12P 000 729; A-side Matrix # 12P 000 729-A1
        - Pet Shop Boys - West End girls, 1985; SR-23321; Pet Shop Boys (Box 388)
          Catalog # V-19206; A-side Matrix # V-1-19206 O B-22679-Z1 11659
        - Peter Panic - A Black man & a Black man, 1992; SR-23322; Peter Panic (Box 388)
          Catalog # BBR-004; A-side Matrix # BBR-004-A
          Bumble Beats Records
        - Peter Panic - A blackman and a blackman ('95 rmx), 1995; SR-23323; Peter Panic (Box 388)
          In same jacket as # SR-23324. 2 copies. Promo
          Catalog # BBR 008; A-side Matrix # BBR.008 A-RE1
        - Peter Panic - A blackman and a blackman ('95 rmx), 1995; SR-23324; Peter Panic (Box 388)
          In same jacket as # SR-23323. 2 copies. Promo
        - Peters, Bernadette - The weekend of a private secretary, 1981; SR-23325; Peters, Bernadette (Box 388)
          Catalog # L33-1734; A-side Matrix # MCA-2705-AM1
        - Peters, D. - See it, hear it, feel it; Mutiny, 1984; SR-23326; Peters, D. (Box 388)
          Catalog # BSR-DP-011; A-side Matrix # BSR-DP-0011-ASUNSHINE-FRANK
        - Peters, Debbie - Boogie with me baby, 1979; SR-23327; Peters, Debbie (Box 388)
          Catalog # JD-11488; A-side Matrix # PD-11488A-10S
          Free Flight
        - Petite - Teens, 1986; SR-23328; Petite (Box 388)
          Catalog # YRC 786-23; A-side Matrix # YRC-786-23-1-A
          York's Records
        - Petworth - Special dedication live, 1983; SR-23329; Petworth (Box 388)
          In same jacket as # SR-23330. 2 copies.
          Catalog # LZ991; A-side Matrix # LZ-991-A
          Full House Records
          Washington, D.C.
        - Petworth - Special dedication live, 1983; SR-23330; Petworth (Box 388)
          In same jacket as # SR-23329. 2 copies.
        - Peyton, Craig - Be thankful for what you got, 1983; SR-23331; Peyton, Craig (Box 388)
          Catalog # PRO-7021-DJ; A-side Matrix # PRO-7021-A
        - PG 13 - Teenage reporter; Rollin' wit da PG, 1990; SR-23332; PG 13 (Box 388)
          Catalog # 15129.1; A-side Matrix # S-24163 15129-A c 36217
          Pump Records
        - Phantom Beats - Stealth, 2000; SR-23333; Phantom Beats (Box 388)
          Catalog # FB 004; A-side Matrix # FB004-A2 08 25011 20 1A1
          Functional Breaks
        - Pharcyde - LabCabinCalifornia (disc one), 1995; SR-23334; Pharcyde (Box 388)
          In same jacket as # SR-23335. Double album.
          Catalog # C1 7243 8 35102 1 4; A-side Matrix # C1-A 35856 1-2
        - Pharcyde - LabCabinCalifornia (disc two), 1995; SR-23335; Pharcyde (Box 388)
          In same jacket as # SR-23334. Double album.
          Catalog # C1 7243 8 35102 1 4; A-side Matrix # C1-C 35857 1-2
        - [Dr. Felix] - It's thinky, 1988; SR-23336; [Dr. Felix] (Box 388)
          In same jacket as # SR-23337; SR-23338. Different discs. Artist unknown
          Catalog # TD 852; A-side Matrix # TD852
          T.D. Records
        - Phase II - The Roxy, 1982; SR-23337; Phase II (Box 388)
          In same jacket as # SR-23336; SR-23338. 2 copies.
          Catalog # AZ/0 159; A-side Matrix # MPO AZ 159 A
          Disc' AZ International
        - Phase II - The Roxy, 1982; SR-23338; Phase II (Box 388)
          In same jacket as # SR-23336; SR-23337. 2 copies.
        - Phase II - The Roxy, 1982; SR-23339; Phase II (Box 388)
        - Phase II - The Roxy, 1982; SR-23340; Phase II (Box 388)
        - Phase II - The Roxy, 1982; SR-23341; Phase II (Box 388)
          In same jacket as # SR-23342. 2 copies.
        - Phase II - The Roxy, 1982; SR-23342; Phase II (Box 388)
          In same jacket as # SR-23341. 2 copies.
        - Phase 2 - The Roxy, 1982; SR-23343; Phase 2; Phase II (Box 388)
          In same jacket as # SR-23344. 2 copies.
          Catalog # CEL 159; A-side Matrix # A-1 CEL-159-A
          Celluloid
        - Phase 2 - The Roxy, 1982; SR-23344; Phase 2; Phase II (Box 388)
          In same jacket as # SR-23343. 2 copies.
        - Phat Doug - Here we go; Hands up high, 1995; SR-23345; Phat Doug (Box 388)
          Catalog # CR-330-DJ; A-side Matrix # CR-330-A-RE1 P.S. A,A,A
          Xcluzive
        - Phatty P - Pass the mic; High volume, 2000; SR-23346; Phatty P (Box 388)
          Catalog # JR011; A-side Matrix # JR011-A
          Juice Recordings
          Gainesville, Florida
        - PHD - Kick that shit and get high; The grand P.O., 1996; SR-23347; PHD (Box 388)
          Catalog # TUF 128086; A-side Matrix # PHD- 8086-A KICK THAT SHIT
          Tuff City
        - Phelon - I see you partyin', 1998; SR-23348; Phelon (Box 388)
          Catalog # INT8P 6453; A-side Matrix # INT8P-6453-A 2
          Interscope Records
        - Phi-Life Cypher - Baddest man, 1998; SR-23349; Phi-Life Cypher (Box 388)
          Catalog # CK001; A-side Matrix # MISCK 001 A-1-1-
          Compressed Knowledge
        - Phil, Dean - I do, 1997; SR-23350; Phil, Dean (Box 388)
          Catalog # 374632032-1; A-side Matrix # 374632032-1A-SP-1
          Motown
        - Phil-Marilyn - Buggs-b-skate, 1980; SR-23351; Phil-Marilyn; Marilyn (Box 388)
          Catalog # DK 00036; A-side Matrix # DJ-0036-A
          Scorpio
          Toronto, Ontario
        - Philadelphia Five - Bump! Jerry, 1988; SR-23352; Philadelphia Five (Box 388)
          Catalog # KK 002; A-side Matrix # KK 002-A1
          KK Records
          Brussels, Belgium
        - Philadelphia Twisting Shoes - Twist is back in town, 1979; SR-23353; Philadelphia Twisting Shoes (Box 388)
          Catalog # Panky 0004; A-side Matrix # N-MS3930-A1
          Panky Records
          Belgium
        - Philaz - Club Ramallah, 2002; SR-23354; Philaz (Box 388)
          Catalog #; A-side Matrix # OR-001-A
          Othaz Records
        - Philips, Chris - Close your eyes, 1994; SR-23355; Philips, Chris (Box 388)
          Catalog # MRC 4499; A-side Matrix # MRC-4499-A
          Metropolitan Recording Corporation
        - Phillips, Claudia - Danny, 1989; SR-23356; Phillips, Claudia (Box 388)
          Catalog # 889 175-1; A-side Matrix # 889 175-1 A
        - Phillips, Esther - Oo oop oo oop, 1979; SR-23357; Phillips, Esther (Box 388)
          Catalog # MK-90; A-side Matrix # T1 MK-90-A-2
        - Phillips, West - (I'm just a) sucker for a pretty face, 1983; SR-23358; Phillips, West (Box 388)
          Catalog # QUS 053; A-side Matrix # QUS 053 A2
          Quality
        - Philly Beat - Voulez vous, 1998; SR-23359; Philly Beat; Sophia (Box 388)
          Catalog # ZYX 8872-12; A-side Matrix # ZYX-8872-12-A1
          Merenberg, Germany
        - Philly Cream - Love can't turn around, 1986; SR-23360; Philly Cream (Box 388)
          Catalog # DMD 970; A-side Matrix # ST-DM-50250-50248-1 1-1
          Cotillion
        - Philly Cream - Love can't turn around, 1986; SR-23361; Philly Cream (Box 388)
        - Philly Crew - P.S. P.S.K. "I'll tell you what it means" the ultimate remix, 1986; SR-23362; Philly Crew; Mac Money (Box 388)
          Catalog # SM-1412; A-side Matrix # SOUNDMAKERS 1412-A
          Place To Be Records
        - Phoenix - (Live, love, laugh) be happy; Comin' to ya, 1982; SR-23363; Phoenix (Box 388)
          Catalog # Z-12001; A-side Matrix # 12-155-15-S "Egg"
          Zanzibar Records & Tapes
          Teaneck, New Jersey
        - Photek - The hidden camera (disc one), 1996; SR-23364; Photek (Box 388)
          In same jacket as # SR-23365. Double album.
          Catalog # QEDDT1; A-side Matrix # QEDDT 1 A-01-01-1
          Science
        - Photek - The hidden camera (disc two), 1996; SR-23365; Photek (Box 388)
          In same jacket as # SR-23364. Double album.
          Catalog # QEDDT1; A-side Matrix # QEDDT 1 C-01-01-1
        - Photek - Modus operandi (disc one), 1997; SR-23366; Photek (Box 388)
          In same jacket as # SR-23367; SR-23368. Triple album. Promo
          Catalog # QEDLPDJ 1; A-side Matrix # STU.QEDLP 1 A-1-1-1
        - Photek - Modus operandi (disc two), 1997; SR-23367; Photek (Box 388)
          In same jacket as # SR-23366; SR-23368. Triple album. Promo
          Catalog # QEDLPDJ 1; A-side Matrix # QEDLP 1 C-1-1-1
        - Photek - Modus operandi (disc three), 1997; SR-23368; Photek (Box 388)
          In same jacket as # SR-23366; SR-23367. Triple album. Promo
          Catalog # QEDLPDJ 1; A-side Matrix # QEDLP 1 E-1-1-1
        - Photek - The hidden camera (disc one), 1996; SR-23369; Photek (Box 388)
          In same jacket as # SR-23370. Double album.
        - Photek - The hidden camera (disc two), 1996; SR-23370; Photek (Box 388)
          In same jacket as # SR-23369. Double album.
        - Photek - Ni - ten - ichi - ryu, 1997; SR-23371; Photek (Box 388)
          Catalog # QEDT 2; A-side Matrix # QEDT 2 A-1-1-1
        - Photek - Modus operandi (disc one), 1997; SR-23372; Photek (Box 388)
          In same jacket as # SR-23373; SR-23374. Triple album. Promo
        - Photek - Modus operandi (disc two), 1997; SR-23373; Photek (Box 388)
          In same jacket as # SR-23372; SR-23374. Triple album. Promo
        - Photek - Modus operandi (disc three), 1997; SR-23374; Photek (Box 388)
          In same jacket as # SR-23372; SR-23373. Triple album. Promo
        - pHrack R - Computer deck aid, 1997; SR-23375; pHrack R (Box 389)
          Catalog # FABR011T; A-side Matrix # FABR-011T-A
          Fused & Bruised
        - Phrenetic System - After the meteor, 1999; SR-23376; Phrenetic System (Box 389)
          Catalog # BONZAI 014; A-side Matrix # BONZAI 014-12-A
          Bonzai Germany
        - Phunkaholics - What tha' dili, 1998; SR-23377; Phunkaholics (Box 389)
          Catalog # AWX 016; A-side Matrix # HAL-127805-A
          Afro Wax Records
        - Phuture - Acid tracks, 1987; SR-23378; Phuture (Box 389)
          Catalog # TX142; A-side Matrix # TX-142-A
          Trax Records
        - Physical Wonders - Return of da phyz (disc one), 1996; SR-23379; Physical Wonders (Box 389)
          In same jacket as # SR-23380. Double album.
          Catalog # PA1022-1; A-side Matrix # PA-1022-1-A EUROPADISK DMM NY USA 15230 B
          Future Records & Tapes
          Landover, Maryland
        - Physical Wonders - Return of da phyz (disc two), 1996; SR-23380; Physical Wonders (Box 389)
          In same jacket as # SR-23379. Double album. Annotated.
          Catalog # PA1022-1; A-side Matrix # PA-1022-1-C EUROPADISK DMM NY USA 15-230 B
        - Piakhan - Wide open, 2000; SR-23381; Piakhan (Box 389)
          Catalog # RDAB-65985-1; A-side Matrix # RDAB-65985-1A RE1
        - Piccalo - Play wit it; No brakes, 2002; SR-23382; Piccalo (Box 389)
          Catalog # TF1305-1; A-side Matrix # TFR-1305-A MIAMI TAPE
          Trunk Funk Records
          Miami Lakes, Florida
        - Pickett, Bobby - Monster rap, 1984; SR-23383; Pickett, Bobby; Paine, Bobby (Box 389)
          Catalog # D.J. EZS-7513; A-side Matrix # EZS-7513-A
          Easy Street Records
        - Pickett, Bobby - Monster rap, 1984; SR-23384; Pickett, Bobby; Paine, Bobby (Box 389)
          Catalog # EZS-7513; A-side Matrix # EZS-7513-A
        - Pickett, Wilson - In Philadelphia, 1970; SR-23385; Pickett, Wilson (Box 389)
          Catalog # SD 8270; A-side Matrix # ST.A.701977-A LW AT
        - Pickett, Wilson - In Philadelphia, 1970; SR-23386; Pickett, Wilson (Box 389)
        - Pickett, Wilson - Right on, 1970; SR-23387; Pickett, Wilson (Box 389)
          Catalog # SD 8250; A-side Matrix # ST.A.691813-B
        - Pickett, Wilson - Funky situation; She's so tight, 1978; SR-23388; Pickett, Wilson (Box 389)
          Catalog # DSKO 128; A-side Matrix # ST-DSKO-35611-2
        - Picotto, Mauro - Komodo, 2000; SR-23389; Picotto, Mauro (Box 389)
          Catalog # BXRG 1094R-12; A-side Matrix # BXRG 1094R 12A
          BXR
        - Picou, Lennox - She funking, 1983; SR-23390; Picou, Lennox (Box 389)
          Catalog # RY-001; A-side Matrix # RY 1 A
          Supertronics
        - Picture Perfect - Prove it, boy, 1986; SR-23391; Picture Perfect (Box 389)
          Catalog # DMD 1000; A-side Matrix # ST DM 51046-1
        - P·I·D - Here we are, 1988; SR-23392; P·I·D (Box 389)
          Catalog # SSR8121; A-side Matrix # SSR 8121 A A+R SP6TF
          Graceland
          Waukegan, Illinois
        - Pieces Of A Dream - Rising to the top, 1988; SR-23393; Pieces Of A Dream (Box 389)
          Catalog # SPRO-04151; A-side Matrix # 22453 B-32911-R1 SPRO-04151-21
        - Pieces Of A Dream - Say la la, 1986; SR-23394; Pieces Of A Dream (Box 389)
          Catalog # V-56022; A-side Matrix # V156022-240928-B Z1
        - Pieces Of A Dream - Ice cream, 1983; SR-23395; Pieces Of A Dream (Box 389)
          Catalog # ED 4928; A-side Matrix # ST-ED-166990-A 2 NS/PH 1-1
        - Pieces Of A Dream - We are one, 1982; SR-23396; Pieces Of A Dream (Box 389)
          Catalog # 60142; A-side Matrix # B-16817 A3 60142-A-3AR 0-1SM1-1 + SLM △1741
        - Pieces Of A Dream - Mt. Airy groove, 1982; SR-23397; Pieces Of A Dream (Box 389)
          Catalog # 0-67967; A-side Matrix # 0-67967AS-1-SP 1-1
        - Pieces Of A Dream - Pieces of a dream, 1981; SR-23398; Pieces Of A Dream (Box 389)
          Catalog # 6E-350; A-side Matrix # SP 0-1 SM1-1 + SLM + △746 6E-350-A-3SH-SP
        - Pierre - Just right, 1984; SR-23399; Pierre (Box 389)
          Catalog # FTR 517; A-side Matrix # FT-517-A
          First Take Records
        - Pierre Moerlen's Gong - Time is the key, 1979; SR-23400; Pierre Moerlen's Gong (Box 389)